Guide to the Executive Committee, Yale Law School Association, Minutes
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Executive committee, Yale Law School Association, minutes
1923-1984
RU 183
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(3 boxes)
The records consist of the constitution and minutes of the executive committee of the Yale Law School Association, the school's alumni association.
Yale Law School Association
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 26-G (YRG 26-G), Records of Yale Law School student, alumni, and support organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of the constitution and minutes of the executive committee of the Yale Law School Association, the school's alumni association.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Minutes (administrative records); Yale Law School; Yale University -- Alumnae and alumnae -- Societies, etc.
- Minutes of the executive committee of the Yale Law School Association, 1923-1984; Accession 1995-A-056
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019
  - Minutes
    - 1923 Jun 18 - 1932 Nov 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1933 Jun 19 - 1941 Mar 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1941 Jun 16 - 1946 Mar 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1946 Jun 21- 1947 Sep 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1947 Oct 14 - 1949 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1950 Feb 22 -1952 Feb 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1952 Jun 16 -1954 Jun 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1954 Nov 12 - 1956 Feb 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1956 Jun 17 - 1957 Jun 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1956 Jun 17 - 1957 Nov 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1957 Nov 1 - 1958 Apr 26 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Oct 31- 1959 Oct 30 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1959 Oct 30 - 1960 Oct 17 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1961 Jun 19 - 1962 Apr 10 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1962 Apr 27 - 1963 Nov 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1964 Apr 21 - 1965 Oct 29 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1966 Apr 29 - 1969 Apr 26 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1969 Nov 21 -1973 May 4 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 1973 Oct 12 -1975 Oct 17 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1976 Apr 30 -1978 Oct 27 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1979 Oct 19 - 1982 Nov 5 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 1983 Apr 15 - 1984 Oct (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Constitutions, 1923-1956 (Box 3, Folder 23)